{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Retrofit Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/40275/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40275,"taskName":"Disability Retrofit","taskDescription":"Modify a Space to Accommodate a Disability","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Retrofit Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":294,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Disability bedroom entrance space disabled","textMessagingName":"Disability Retrofit","rolloverLongDesc":"Make relatively minor changes such as adding grab bars, widening a door \u0026 lowering a threshold in order to make the space safer \u0026 more practical for a person with a disability. See separate categories for full-scale remodeling to accommodate disabilities \u0026 for someone who simple analyzes \u0026 plans the adaptations.","rolloverShortDesc":"Minor alterations to meet needs of disabled.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Modify a Space to Accommodate a Disability.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Retrofit \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Retrofit a Home for Disability, Accessibility \u0026 More","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":20,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Disability Retrofit","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Disability Retrofit","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Disability Retrofit Project","urlName":"Disability-Retrofit","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home \u0026 Disability Retrofit Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Disability,bedroom,entrance,space,disabled,handycap,handicap,consultant,designer,accommodate","emcCategoryOid":-12021,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":578,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40275/":{"taskOID":40275,"originalTaskOID":40275,"setID":578,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4434,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Disability","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the disability? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6946,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wheelchair","answerDisplayText":"Wheelchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6731,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walker","answerDisplayText":"Walker","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3144,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Impaired vision","answerDisplayText":"Impaired vision","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3142,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Impaired hearing","answerDisplayText":"Impaired hearing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3143,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Impaired strength/motion range (reaching, bending, lifting)","answerDisplayText":"Impaired strength/motion range (reaching, bending, lifting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5569,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (gripping, turning, twisting knobs etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (gripping, turning, twisting knobs etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3669,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Loss of balance, coordination","answerDisplayText":"Loss of balance, coordination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5568,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Sense of smell","answerDisplayText":"Sense of smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1472,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cognitive issues (dementia, Alzheimer's, memory loss)","answerDisplayText":"Cognitive issues (dementia, Alzheimer's, memory loss)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4651,"questionDisplayText":"Location of problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where are you having trouble in the home? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2804,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Getting in and outside","answerDisplayText":"Getting in and outside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3989,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Moving from room to room","answerDisplayText":"Moving from room to room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4427,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Opening doors/turning knobs","answerDisplayText":"Opening doors/turning knobs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2805,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Getting up and down","answerDisplayText":"Getting up and down","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2910,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hallway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Hallway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1457,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Closet(s)","answerDisplayText":"Closet(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2549,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Floors","answerDisplayText":"Floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4484,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Outdoors (garage, walkways, driveway)","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors (garage, walkways, driveway)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4433,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Residence","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of residence is it?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4393,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"One-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6565,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"Two-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6603,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5572,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","answerDisplayText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4434,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Disability","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of the disability? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6946,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wheelchair","answerDisplayText":"Wheelchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6731,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walker","answerDisplayText":"Walker","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3144,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Impaired vision","answerDisplayText":"Impaired vision","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3142,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Impaired hearing","answerDisplayText":"Impaired hearing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3143,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Impaired strength/motion range (reaching, bending, lifting)","answerDisplayText":"Impaired strength/motion range (reaching, bending, lifting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5569,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (gripping, turning, twisting knobs etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (gripping, turning, twisting knobs etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3669,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Loss of balance, coordination","answerDisplayText":"Loss of balance, coordination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5568,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Sense of smell","answerDisplayText":"Sense of smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1472,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cognitive issues (dementia, Alzheimer's, memory loss)","answerDisplayText":"Cognitive issues (dementia, Alzheimer's, memory loss)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6946,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wheelchair","answerDisplayText":"Wheelchair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6731,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walker","answerDisplayText":"Walker","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3144,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Impaired vision","answerDisplayText":"Impaired vision","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3142,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Impaired hearing","answerDisplayText":"Impaired hearing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3143,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Impaired strength/motion range (reaching, bending, lifting)","answerDisplayText":"Impaired strength/motion range (reaching, bending, lifting)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5569,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (gripping, turning, twisting knobs etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Sense of touch/dexterity (gripping, turning, twisting knobs etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3669,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Loss of balance, coordination","answerDisplayText":"Loss of balance, coordination","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5568,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Sense of smell","answerDisplayText":"Sense of smell","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1472,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Cognitive issues (dementia, Alzheimer's, memory loss)","answerDisplayText":"Cognitive issues (dementia, Alzheimer's, memory loss)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4651,"questionDisplayText":"Location of problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where are you having trouble in the home? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2804,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Getting in and outside","answerDisplayText":"Getting in and outside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3989,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Moving from room to room","answerDisplayText":"Moving from room to room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4427,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Opening doors/turning knobs","answerDisplayText":"Opening doors/turning knobs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2805,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Getting up and down","answerDisplayText":"Getting up and down","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2910,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hallway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Hallway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1457,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Closet(s)","answerDisplayText":"Closet(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2549,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Floors","answerDisplayText":"Floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4484,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Outdoors (garage, walkways, driveway)","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors (garage, walkways, driveway)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2804,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Getting in and outside","answerDisplayText":"Getting in and outside","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3989,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Moving from room to room","answerDisplayText":"Moving from room to room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4427,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Opening doors/turning knobs","answerDisplayText":"Opening doors/turning knobs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2805,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Getting up and down","answerDisplayText":"Getting up and down","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2910,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Hallway(s)","answerDisplayText":"Hallway(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1457,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Closet(s)","answerDisplayText":"Closet(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3594,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Lighting","answerDisplayText":"Lighting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2549,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Floors","answerDisplayText":"Floors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4484,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Outdoors (garage, walkways, driveway)","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors (garage, walkways, driveway)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4433,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Residence","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of residence is it?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4393,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"One-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6565,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"Two-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6603,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5572,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","answerDisplayText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4393,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"One-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6565,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two-story single family home","answerDisplayText":"Two-story single family home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6603,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on ground floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhouse, apartment etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6604,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","answerDisplayText":"Unit on upper floor of multi-family residence (condo, townhhouse, apt., etc.)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5572,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","answerDisplayText":"Separate apt./quarters adjacent to family residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}